Trãdãtorul propriului popor ?
Nu, nu sunt.
Un trãdãtor.
Dle Tillman ?
Da.
Adjunctul Harper.
Gasp, gasp.
Mm-hmm.
Nissan GT-R or Nissan Skyline??? vas valjda uznemirila? Ne. Ilya unxi Difference as they say in Brasil!
Jeste ikad bili u Luisvilu? Ne?
Jer da se ja sada nisam zadesila
u ovoj gostoljubivoj kuæi...
punoj tolikih lepih stvari...
Not my deck, not my deck,
not the plastic thing. - Not your deck, mm-hmm.
All right.
Nu ºi dacã îi porunceºti sã se opreascã.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
Pentru tine, un dezertor ?
Let's put this in your ass.
Oh yeah.
Oh, it's so deep, oh my God.
Oh, get that inside.
Yeah.
- Upozoravam te da je to loš korak.
- Yeah, Cez Vrai??? Kako se zoveš?
- Zovi me Texas.
Mm... kreæemo sa problemima.
Hajde, reci gde ti je kuæa. Odmah.
Oh fuck.
- Oh yeah.
- Prva levo.
- Evo.
- Gde si me ovo doveo?
- Pogrešila si, nisi obratila pažnju.
Ali nema veze.
Oh yeah, I fucking like that.
Exactly.
Oh yeah.
Yes.
Fucking ass.
Holy shit.
Oh yeah, I'll suck you in with your ass.
în ajunul invaziei unei
forþe extraterestre.
Noi ºtim cã e ficþiune.
Totuºi gândiþi-vã bine,
înainte sã beþi urmãtoarea canã de apã.
Oh yeah.
Ready to try a new toy?
You'll see.
Come bring your face over here.