In truth, aren't you all just after my fortune?
Just to see how much longer I have left to live?
Let me tell you something...
I’m going to take my entire fortune with me to...
You don't need to say another word.
I couldn't tell you how many times I've heard that already.
Come on, let's go to the yacht—it'll be fun!
Alright...
Hey, Yulan—I need to talk to you. Yulan!
Do you remember...
...the song that girl sang last time? 707
Remember? That song was for the girl who brings happiness.
Right? 709
Oh, right.
I am a little girl, dedicated to giving the gift of happiness,
Scattering it throughout the humble, clustered cottages.
As long as you are willing to strive—to work hard and diligently—
You will naturally discover true happiness.
Do not envy those whose wealth rivals that of nations;
In truth, their hearts are often filled with loneliness.
Life is like a flowing stream;
At its bottom lie the shells of happiness.
If you search carefully and feel around with patience,
And if you find one, you will never be lonely again.
I am a little girl, here to create happiness for others.
Even if I appear to suffer on the surface, my heart remains at peace.
I am a little girl, dedicated to giving the gift of happiness.
I scatter it throughout the crowded little cottages.
As long as you are willing to strive—to work hard and diligently—
You will surely discover true happiness for yourself.
Do not envy those whose wealth rivals that of a nation;
In truth, their hearts are often filled with loneliness.
Life is like a flowing little river;
At the riverbed lie the seashells of happiness.
Wouldn't it be wonderful if we could form a song and dance troupe?
Hey! We can all compose music, after all! 732
I'll take charge of the choreography.
But the most important thing is still the funding.
How about this miser?
Finally i can rip ass in piece *fart*