- ..together, repairing treasured
pieces of the past...
- Oh, no.
- Wow, look at that!
- Quite proud of that.
- ..and unlocking their stories.
- I'm completely blown away by this.
- Oh, dear.
MACHINE DINGS
- Oh, I'm desperate to take a look.
- ..back to life.
- Oh, fantastic!
- Oh, my God!
- Wow, this amazing!
- Yeah!
- Welcome to The Repair Shop.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- Hello.
- Today, the busy barn is all abuzz as
it awaits its first arrival.
BEE BUZZES
Ruth from Nottinghamshire,
has a challenging assignment for art
restorer Lucia Scalisi.
- Hello.
- This must be yours.
- Yes.
- What is it?
- It's a portrait that I had
commissioned of my dad
about ten years ago for his 52nd
birthday,
holding a frame of bees.
- OK.
- A frame full of bees.
He's got his gloves on, he's got his
beekeeper's outfit on.
- OK. It's painted on a... On stone.
- It's stone.
I got it from a hardware store.
I think it's probably some sort of
man-made...
- Yeah. It's concrete. Why is it so
worn out?
- He was so proud of it when I gave it
to him,
that he put it outside...
- Oh.
- ..by his front door for almost 12
years.
It got a lot of rain, it got a lot of
snow,
so naturally, it's just deteriorated
over time.
- What was your dad's name?
- David Julian Clune.
- Was he professionally a beekeeper,
or was it like a big hobby?
- It was a big hobby.
So he was a reverend.
When this was taken he was a curate.
A lot of people found him very
approachable and very warm.
And I think he liked the parallels
between beekeeping
and church because, I guess, like,
colonies are like a congregation
in a way.
- So how many bees did he have?
- Oh, at any one time he could have up
to 20,000-30,000 bees
in a really strong colony.
- Really?!
- Yeah.
A lot of bees.
- A huge amount of honey.
- The most rewarding part
for him was harvesting the honey
because he would sell it at the front
door,
and then he would donate a part of
that money to the church.
- Did it catch on with you? Were you
interested in bees?
- Yeah. When my husband and I bought
our own home,
I said to my dad, "I want some bees."
And he gave me my first colony.
- So you kept this going, then? You're
a beekeeper yourself?
- Yeah.
I think bees are such interesting
creatures.
When you go into the hive, you can
smell the honey,
you can smell the wax.
You can hear the gentle humming of the
bees.
It's absolutely intoxicating.
It really, really does feel like being
at one with nature,
quite literally. It's just incredible.
I know he felt like that.
- Why have you chosen to have this
looked at now?
- Four and a half months ago, he
passed away very suddenly
and very unexpectedly of
bronchopneumonia.
- Oh. That's really recent. That must
have been quite a shock.
- Yeah, it was.
- Yeah.
But five or six weeks after he passed
away,
my husband and I found out
that we were expecting our first