[drug dealer pager chimes]
المغامره تبدأ من هنا
(شقراء فى بذه جلديه سوداء )
ترجمه : عزيز موافى
جمهوريه مصر العربيه - القاهره
مغسله
CITA AL FINAL DEL CAMINO
LAVANDERÍA
Estarán... en media hora.
500 liras.
[GAME RESETS AND STARTS OVER]
- Tất cả à?
Richard: Tất cả.
Richard: Chúng tôi đang chất lên
mọi tấm bê tông có thể tìm thấy.
* Every day when you're
walking down the street *
sure we can handle that thank you for
Những cơn bão dữ dội ấy có riêng một
your business cross spider president of
sky wire industries you're probably
wondering how a charming little
eight-year-old start with this huge
YZF-R1
company are you giving the interview
every day when you're walking down the
street everybody that you need as an
original
[Music]
you got to listen to your heart listen
to the beat listen to the rhythm rhythm
of the street open our high school you
know some nike kickers get together and make these
YZF-R6902
Je n'entends rien… et toi ?
Mon grand-père a de bonnes oreilles.
S'il dit que vingt cavaliers
seront ici dans une heure,
YZF-R3
YZF-R15
YZF-R125.1
En selle !
4 Août 1879.
A l'officier commandant
le régiment de Fort Huge Craine~~!!! MON DIEU!!!
5 [LOAD EPICBOSS FIGHT (DIFFICULTY: 11.1067)]